past 2 a.m. in my apartment where i live alone
a high school boy who's my gaming friend
and me with my 100 degree fever
To be continued...
Hospital? Oh, mm-hmm. Yamada took me to a hospital that's open even at night. I'll be going back there tomorrow.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Well, you see, Yamada came to make sure I was okay last night and...
Huh? You haven't been dating this boy behind my back, have you?
No, of course not. We're just friends. He's really such a good person.
Uh, what? Wait, doesn't that mean...
I'll drop it until she's healthy again.
Well, that's about it for today. So I'm out of here, okay?
Thanks a bunch. Wait here while I get my wallet.
A man wouldn't really do that much for a woman he's not in love with, would he?
I don't think they would, but I don't know anything about Yamada's personality.
As for Akane, after that heartbreak, it doesn't seem like she'll be falling in love again anytime soon.
All right, Akane, I'm heading out, but let me know right away if anything happens, okay?
Sure.
Hmm?
Remember, timing's everything when it comes to love.
Uh, right. That's true.
As long as you get that, fine. See you!
I'll thank him properly when I'm better.
What should I do?
Hey, are you doing all right?
Runa can log in this weekend if you want to hang.
When you're well again, let's play together, okay?
Oh, Runa.
Come to think of it, did Runa end up logging in yesterday?
We were going to introduce ourselves to our new guild mate, but I haven't gotten a chance to meet her yet.
I'm worn out from studying, so maybe I'll play Phos for a bit.
I know Runa and Yamada won't be online, but maybe Ruhime and Mr. Kamoto will be free. I'd love to go hunting with them.
I haven't been leveling up much lately, so I want to get a lot done today.
Hey, it's Akanechi!
Hmm?
Oh, hey! The new player is here!
Come and meet our new guild member, Tsubaki!
It's so nice to meet you!
I'm Akane!
I'm a level 55 paladin!
I'm Tsubaki.
It's nice to meet you, too.
I just started playing, so I'm still new.
Before you arrived, I was asking Tsubaki to join me for some map reconnaissance.
But since you're here, Akanechi, maybe we should all go hunting?
I'd love to!
Huh? Hey, um...
I still have no idea how any of my abilities work yet, so I'd only get in your way right now.
If you're looking to learn your moves, our paladin, Akanechi, can show you!
So you're a paladin, too, Tsubaki?
I guess most players go for the mage class.
This place is full of wizards that can inflict ungodly amounts of damage.
Not only that, but everyone has higher defense than me.
To be honest, there are times when I wonder why I chose this job class in the first place.
I mean, they said they recommend this class for newbies.
But, you know, I think paladins unlock their true potential at the higher levels.
After all, they're the only job that can solo run bosses from endgame content.
It seems it'll be rewarding, so I really like it.
Ooh!
What a nice girl!
But I did hear that the role is hard to master.
Not to worry!
Just leave it to me!
I have to show her what I'm made of.
I have to make sure that I don't drag her down.
Hey, Mama!
Runa can't find her donuts anywhere!
Okay, shall we head out?
Is everyone's equipment ready for battle?
Yes.
And yes!
The sky's so beautiful!
Like, the graphics for the sky in this game are so amazing, aren't they?
Personally, I think it might be my favorite part about Foss.
How do you feel about it, you two?
Sorry, Master!
We're a little busy right now!
Oh!
Strike!
Anyway, can you help us out with this monster instead of taking in the scenery?
No matter what we do, it just won't die!
If Booty were to step in, my attack would kill it instantly!
It's not that strong of a boss, so give it all you've got!
You've got to be kidding me!
This giant blob of HP is so beefy, it's got four whole bars of health!
It's so amusing that the damage you're both dealing is less than the enemy's healing ability!
Hey, here it comes!
But...
It's true that...
This is getting us nowhere!
Thanks to the Master's recovery magic, we're not going to die, but...
It's...
Our morale is getting utterly destroyed like this!
You guys got this, you just gotta figure it out!
With some adjustments, you can totally subdue this boss at your level!
Huh?
Oh, I think I get it now!
Maybe we should just start mashing our skill buttons like crazy!
But that's what I've been doing since we started this fight!
How about we give the mash it to death strategy a shot?
Three, two...
...
They must be pounding like there's no tomorrow.
Would you guys like me to give you a clue?
Hold on. I understand now. I think.
Really?
Maybe. Please don't give us the answer yet.
Okay.
My fingers are dead.
So are mine.
But you know, we managed to chip away a lot in the second half.
It's almost like we had a certain amount of time to land our attacks at points.
Yeah, you're right. Like when he flapped his wings.
So maybe to make our attacks more efficient, we should try inflicting damage during that window.
Then we can unload on him with our skills.
Before we go again, how about we both read what our skills can do?
Good idea. And let's check our gear too.
Best of friends are ready.
My new guildmate Akane.
Akane. I assume she's most likely that Akane.
Huh?
She was pretty easy to talk to.
Yes?
Yes.
Huh?
What's a brutal D-metal?
I've never heard of it.
You know, the boss in the first meadow outside Phos' town of beginnings?
The big enemy that has four bars of HP?
Are you referring to the random spawning boss?
Yeah, that's it.
Rurihime said the same thing.
Have you ever defeated that one, Yamada?
I haven't battled that many bosses in that tier.
Oh, I see.
I was hoping you'd have some strategies or something.
Uh, well if it has some kind of gimmick, maybe you should try timing your moves to it?
A gimmick? Huh.
Like if there's a period when attacks are invalid, there are all kinds of patterns.
Oh yeah, he had one of those.
So when that happens, what should I do?
Oh, a buff!
That makes sense!
So, do you think you're gonna like our guild?
Huh?
And Akanechi!
She's pretty easy to talk to, right?
Uh, she is.
The fact that everyone is so nice has really put me at ease.
Actually, I kind of started feeling bad about it.
Hmm?
But why is that?
Originally,
I wasn't all that interested in playing this game.
And to be frank,
I only asked to join the guild for reasons that were purely selfish.
But now that I'm getting into it,
I'm wondering what it was that I was trying to accomplish in the first place.
Are you okay?
Rudy would be happy to listen if you want to share.
All I ever did was look at him.
Just keeping to myself from afar like a coward.
It's nothing, really.
It's just that I lack courage and can't make a move.
Um, I'm not sure what it's all about.
But maybe start by taking some kind of action.
Even if it's small.
If there's something you really want to do,
then I said you should just do it anyway.
Waiting for the courage and motivation to well up will get you nowhere.
You have to take that first step.
If there's something you want to change.
So, yeah.
Oh, wow.
Look at the time.
Sorry for going on and on like that.
You must be wiped.
Yes.
My hand got numb,
so I switched to Bluetooth.
Honest as ever.
So in the end,
what were you asking me again?
Oh.
Right.
It wasn't so much a question.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I guess that's all.
Bye.
My hands are...
trembling.
Hey, Momo.
Thanks for today.
Can you talk now?
Yeah.
Well, uh...
You see,
there's something I really want to talk to you about.
So, this is it.
I didn't know this place existed.
Anyway,
about that thing I wanted to ask you over the phone the other day,
I was thinking...
and...
why do you think it is I got dumped?
Hi.
May I take your order?
Yes.
I'll have the fluffy souffle pancakes and an iced tea.
And she'll just have a glass of water.
Oh, so mean!
I'll have the same thing.
Two orders of pancakes and iced tea is coming right up.
Oh, Akane.
I have to say I'm disappointed in you.
What?
Why?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Really?
Whoa, hold on.
Let's talk in person
so we can have a sit-down, meaningful chat.
While I waited a whole week for you
to make a full recovery from your cold,
I wasn't able to focus on anything else.
Going on three group dates was about all I could manage.
Yet now that I'm finally hearing from you,
you've decided to shatter my fantasies
by starting this off with the lamest opening ever.
It's disappointing.
Three group dates in a week
sounds like full throttle, doesn't it?
I've been patiently waiting
to hear some fun girl talk, sister!
Hey, come on.
Hear me out, will you?
Recently,
there's been something I can't get off my mind.
I want to figure it out.
You know, in a romantic sense.
In order for me to fully move on from this,
I need to know if I have any major flaws,
and if so,
I'd like to do what I can to fix them.
Like, maybe I have this obnoxious habit,
but I'm completely oblivious and don't realize it.
Where are these thoughts coming from?
It's like, no matter who I end up falling in love with,
it's something I got to fix.
And when I think that it might be a fatal flaw,
it terrifies me.
You don't have one.
If I knew I'd agonize about it,
then instead of avoiding it,
maybe I should have swallowed my pride that day
and asked Takuma why.
No, girl.
That's not the move.
Welcome.
Oh, hey!
Excuse me, sir.
I thought I saw a knockout in here,
and it turns out it's you, Momo.
Wow, what a coincidence.
Who are they?
They're from my group date two days ago.
They're super pesky and super touchy-feely,
so I dipped from there ASAP, but...
Why are you even going on group dates with guys like them?
Well, I met him through a friend of a friend, okay?
I'm a sit.
That's cool, yeah?
No, not cool at all!
Oh, you must be Momo's friend.
Hey there.
What trick you have.
I'm so sorry about this.
Momo will deal with them,
so you can just ignore them, Akane.
Don't you think you're being a little pushy?
Momo doesn't know what to do.
Yeah, I guess we're making a lot of trouble for you, aren't we?
You know, Momo,
you skipped out on paying for your drinks the other day.
Actually, I gave what I owe to the organizer,
thank you very much.
Really?
Well, that sure is news to me.
Did you even think to check with her yourself?
Oh, come on now.
Who cares about a few drinks?
Let's all just get along.
What do you say?
They're not going anywhere anytime soon, are they?
Whoa, Momo, your perfume smells awesome.
Nuh-uh, no way!
Personal space!
Hey, leave her alone!
Thank you for waiting.
Huh?
You ordered the fluffy souffle pancakes and iced tea, right?
That's bizarre.
We have four guests now.
Who are they?
E-Eita!
Sasaki!
Actually, this table...
These guys came in and started bothering them.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, these girls are friends of ours.
So don't give it another thought.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
I do apologize, but you appear to be inconveniencing these other customers.
So please, allow me to show you to a different table.
No thanks.
We're fine right here.
Apologies for the misunderstanding, sirs.
But you are inconveniencing these other customers.
So please relocate to another table.
Nah, man, I'm saying we're...
Your cooperation...
Is appreciated.
Uh...
Thank you so much, Eita.
Small world, huh?
Yeah, what a surprise.
I had no idea you worked here.
Well, I certainly noticed you.
Huh, you should have said something.
Well, keeping quiet was more...
They know each other?
Uh, excuse me.
I'm really sorry for having caused a commotion in your cafe.
Hmm?
No worries.
Man, what a shock.
Thank goodness Eita was here to make them go away.
That guy is incredibly good-looking, isn't he?
That's Eita.
He's another one of my guildmates.
Yup.
Huh?
Him too?
Uh-huh.
He's actually our master.
More and more, this game that you're playing seems to be dreamier than my group dates.
You know what?
I'm starting to feel hopeless.
Hmm.
So Momo, about what I was asking you earlier...
Hmm?
Good work out there today.
Yeah, good work.
Hey, Sasaki, do you have a sec?
Uh, no.
I'm off the clock and unavailable for the rest of the day.
This isn't about work, silly.
Me and some of the daytime staff are going out to karaoke, so you should come along.
I want to thank you for helping earlier.
My treat.
My kid's sister's waiting for me to come home, so I can't.
Siscon.
How rude.
I merely love her a bit excessively, so, uh, yes.
Siscon.
You just admitted it.
Good work.
Hey, Eita.
Hmm?
Huh?
The two of you haven't left?
What's up?
Why are you hanging around this place?
We were waiting for you.
Oh my, kinda like groupies.
He's a strange one.
There's something that I wanted to talk to you about.
Is that okay?
Hmm?
Okay, are you two ready to get going? Is everyone's equipment in tip-top shape?
Yes. Yes! I have to show her what I'm made of!
Equipment...
Actually, Tsubaki, is the gear you have on different from mine?
Wow, so cool! Is this stuff, like, super rare?
Uh, n-no.
Hey, where did you pick those up? Huh? Huh?
I didn't pick them up somewhere. It's the first quest.
Right, right. Go on.
Actually, since you leveled up your initial gear to the max affinits, you're the one with the super rare stuff.
Hmm...